(this["webpackJsonpdropdown-menu-navbar"]=this["webpackJsonpdropdown-menu-navbar"]||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,t,s){},15:function(e,t,s){"use strict";s.r(t);var n=s(1),o=s.n(n),r=s(3),i=s.n(r),a=s(4),c=s(5),l=s(8),u=s(6),d=(s(13),[{question:"_____ provides long distance transmission of data over large geographic areas",answers:["LAN","MAN","PAN","WAN"],correct:"WAN",questionId:"099099"},{question:"The function performed by data link layer is ____",answers:["Line configuration","Routing","Physical addressing","Encryption"],correct:"Physical addressing",questionId:"267908"},{question:"TCP/IP protocol suite is made of _____ layers",answers:["Seven","Six","Five","Three"],correct:"Five",questionId:"333247"},{question:"_____ used to represent digital data by using digital signals",answers:["Digital to Digital conversion","Analog to Digital conversion","Digital to Analog conversion","Analog to Analog conversion"],correct:"Digital to Digital conversion",questionId:"496293"},{question:"In ____, use two levels of voltage amplitude",answers:["Unipolar NRZ","Polar NRZ","Bipolar","AMI"],correct:"Polar NRZ",questionId:"588909"},{question:"In _____ technique, each data bit replaced with n bits using a spreading code",answers:["FHSS","DSSS","Both a and b","None of the above"],correct:"DSSS",questionId:"648452"},{question:"RG \u2013 59 is category of _____ cable",answers:["Twisted Pair","Fibre Optic","Coaxial","Unguided medium"],correct:"Coaxial",questionId:"786649"},{question:"____ operates only in physical layer",answers:["Repeater","Bridge","Router","Gateway"],correct:"Repeater",questionId:"839754"},{question:"The _______ layer is responsible for movements of individual bits from one hop (node) to the next",answers:["Physical","Data Link","Transport","Network"],correct:"Physical",questionId:"98390"},{question:"The _______ data link layer is responsible for moving frames from one hop (node) to the next",answers:["Physical","Data Link","Transport","Network"],correct:"Data Link",questionId:"1071006"},{question:"The ________ layer is responsible for providing services to the user",answers:["Session","Presentation","Application","Network"],correct:"Application",questionId:"1174154"},{question:"The ________ layer is responsible for translation,compression, and encryption",answers:["Session","Presentation","Transport","Network"],correct:"Presentation",questionId:"1226535"},{question:"The ______ layer is responsible for dialog control and synchronization",answers:["Session"," Data Link","Transport","Network"],correct:"Session",questionId:"1310938"},{question:"The ______ layer is responsible for the delivery of a message from one process to another",answers:["Physical","Data Link","Transport","Network"],correct:"Transport",questionId:"1436873"},{question:"The ______ layer is responsible for the delivery of individual packets from the source host to the destination host",answers:["Physical","Data Link","Transport","Network"],correct:"Network",questionId:"1515110"}]),_=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:5;return Promise.resolve(d.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e))},p=s(7),h=s(0),g=function(e){var t=e.question,s=e.options,o=e.selected,r=Object(n.useState)(s),i=Object(p.a)(r,2),a=i[0],c=i[1];return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"questionBox",children:[Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"question",children:t}),a.map((function(e,t){return Object(h.jsx)("button",{className:"answerBtn",onClick:function(){c([e]),o(e)},children:e},t)}))]})},f=function(e){var t=e.score,s=e.playAgain;return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-board",children:[Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"score",children:["You scored ",t," / 5 correct answers!"]}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{className:"playBtn",onClick:s,children:"Play again!"})]})},v=function(e){Object(l.a)(s,e);var t=Object(u.a)(s);function s(){var e;Object(a.a)(this,s);for(var n=arguments.length,o=new Array(n),r=0;r<n;r++)o[r]=arguments[r];return(e=t.call.apply(t,[this].concat(o))).state={questionBank:[],score:0,responses:0},e.getQuestions=function(){_().then((function(t){e.setState({questionBank:t})}))},e.computeAnswer=function(t,s){t===s&&e.setState({score:e.state.score+1}),e.setState({responses:e.state.responses<5?e.state.responses+1:5})},e.playAgain=function(){e.getQuestions(),e.setState({score:0,responses:0})},e}return Object(c.a)(s,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.getQuestions()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"container",children:[Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"title",children:"QuizApp"}),this.state.questionBank.length>0&&this.state.responses<5&&this.state.questionBank.map((function(t){var s=t.question,n=t.answers,o=t.correct,r=t.questionId;return Object(h.jsx)(g,{question:s,options:n,selected:function(t){return e.computeAnswer(t,o)}},r)})),5===this.state.responses?Object(h.jsx)(f,{score:this.state.score,playAgain:this.playAgain}):null]})}}]),s}(n.Component);i.a.render(Object(h.jsx)(o.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(h.jsx)(v,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[15,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.3e930f2b.chunk.js.map